<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTD-8" ?>

<NewsList>
	<News>
		<Title>Fact Check: Did Benjamin Netanyahu Run Into A Bunker During Iran's Missile Attack?</Title>
		<Content>Following Iran's massive rocket attack on Israel Tuesday night, video clips circulating on social media showed Israeli Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu allegedly running for cover inside a bunker. As Iran's missiles, some of which 	were hypersonic, entered Israeli airspace, sirens were sounded across the country, prompting thousands to seek safety.
		</Content>
		<Link>https://www.ndtv.com/world-news/israel-iran-missile-attack-fact-check-did-benjamin-netanyahu-run-into-a-bunker-during-irans-missile-attack-6698839</Link>
	</News>

	<News>
		<Title>India vs Bangladesh 2nd Test Day 5 Highlights: IND win by 7 wickets, record 2-0 series victory</Title>
		<Content>India fought Bangladesh and time to wrestle a victory in the second Test by seven wickets. They have thus won the series 2-0 and all but sealed a spot in the World Test Championship final for the third consecutive time. The bowlers followed up on the utterly ridiculous work done by the Indian batters on Day 4 by dismissing Bangladesh for a score of 146 in their second innings in the first session.</Content>
		<Link>https://www.hindustantimes.com/cricket/india-vs-bangladesh-live-score-2nd-test-match-day-5-ind-vs-ban-2024-latest-cricket-scorecard-kanpur-today-october-1-101727717629723.html</Link>
	</News>

	<News>
		<Title>Cocaine worth ₹2,000 crore seized in Delhi's biggest drug bust</Title>
		<Content>The Delhi police today seized over 560 kg of cocaine worth nearly ₹2,000 crore, in one of the biggest drug bust in the national capital. The drugs were found in South Delhi's Mehrauli and four people have been arrested in the case, police said.</Content>
		<Link>https://www.hindustantimes.com/india-news/cocaine-worth-rs-2-000-crore-seized-in-delhis-biggest-drug-bust-101727861086019.html</Link>
	</News>

	<News>
		<Title>Israel denies entry to U.N. Secretary General Antonio Guterres amid tensions with Iran</Title>
		<Content>Israel's Foreign Minister announced on Wednesday, October 2, that U.N. Secretary General Antonio Guterres has been barred from entering the country."Today, I have declared UN Secretary-General @antonioguterres persona non grata in Israel and banned him from entering the country. Anyone who cannot unequivocally condemn Iran's heinous attack on Israel, as almost every country in the world has done, does not deserve to step foot on Israeli soil. This is a Secretary-General who has yet to denounce the massacre and sexual atrocities committed by Hamas murderers on October 7, nor has he led any efforts to declare them a terrorist organization," Israel’s Minister of Foreign Affairs said in a post on X (formerly Twitter).</Content>
		<Link>https://www.hindustantimes.com/india-news/cocaine-worth-rs-2-000-crore-seized-in-delhis-biggest-drug-bust-101727861086019.html</Link>
	</News>

	<News>
		<Title>'BJP's compulsion': Prashant Kishor attacks Nitish Kumar, calls him mentally unfit</Title>
		<Content>Prashant Kishor said in an interview that the people of Bihar will sideline the two main alliances and hand over his new political party an absolute majority in the assembly.

Prashant Kishor said Nitish Kumar isn't in the right physical, mental and political state to run Bihar.

He said the people of Bihar will punish the BJP for backing Nitish Kumar.

"The Congress helped Lalu Prasad run a 'jungle raj' for 15 years. The people of Bihar completely uprooted the Congress. The BJP will suffer the same fate," he said.

He said backing Nitish Kumar is the BJP's political compulsion.

"It knows that its alliance will lose if he remains at the helm, but it is the political compulsion of the BJP," he added.</Content>
		<Link>https://www.moneycontrol.com/news/business/economy/what-does-middle-east-tensions-oil-price-spike-mean-for-indias-macro-picture-12834146.html</Link>
	</News>
</NewsList>

